<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>QuantaQuill</title>
    <link>https://quanta-naut.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on QuantaQuill</description>
    <image>
      <title>QuantaQuill</title>
      <url>https://quanta-naut.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://quanta-naut.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.139.2</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://quanta-naut.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simulation Of Lorenz Attractor, The Chaos Theory.</title>
      <link>https://quanta-naut.github.io/posts/simulation-of-lorenz-attractor-the-chaos-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quanta-naut.github.io/posts/simulation-of-lorenz-attractor-the-chaos-theory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;Thumbnail.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-exploring-the-chaos-of-the-lorenz-attractor&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction: Exploring the Chaos of the Lorenz Attractor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered how something as simple as a set of equations can create intricate and mesmerizing patterns? The Lorenz Attractor is a perfect example of this phenomenon—a beautiful yet chaotic system that has fascinated scientists, mathematicians, and hobbyists alike for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally derived by Edward Lorenz in 1963 while studying atmospheric convection, the Lorenz Attractor is a set of three differential equations that exhibit chaotic behavior under certain conditions. It’s often cited as a classic example of chaos theory, illustrating how small changes in initial conditions can lead to wildly different outcomes—popularly referred to as the &amp;ldquo;butterfly effect.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Blog!!!</title>
      <link>https://quanta-naut.github.io/posts/my-first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://quanta-naut.github.io/posts/my-first-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;title&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blast Off! Welcome to My Journey of Rockets and Code&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my blog! I’m thrilled to share my projects, passion, and progress in the exciting worlds of rocketry and programming. This space will be a blend of technical insights, creative experiments, and updates on my journey to build and launch rockets while sharpening my coding skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-to-expect&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Expect:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rocketry Adventures:&lt;/strong&gt; I am actively working on my rocket that is set to reach an apogee of 1km and hopefully be recovered without any damage. Here I will be sharing my updates and build process, and many more to come.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programming Projects:&lt;/strong&gt; I am very much interested in programming, more like interested in creating simulation using programming. I will be sharing detailed posts on the projects I make here. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/tarun-kumar-s-676a74267/%22&#34;&gt;My LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; for the projects I worked on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress Updates:&lt;/strong&gt; Stay tuned for real-time updates on my experiments and achievements, and perhaps a few lessons learned along the way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-this-blog&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why This Blog:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made this blog site to document and express myself. Here I will share all my updates that will be useful for some one or the other. And also I will have it as my memory so that I can have fun time reading all the work I did, while reading it in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
